(Captions are auto-generated)
The left wing lunatics are
trying very hard to bring back
COVID lockdowns and mandates
with all of their sudden fear
mongering about the new variants
that are coming.
Gee whiz,
you know what else is coming?
An election.
They want to restart the COVID
hysteria so they can justify
more lockdowns,
more censorship,
more illegal drop boxes,
more mail in ballots,
and trillions of dollars in
payoffs to their political
allies heading into the 2024
election.
Does that sound familiar?
These are bad people.
These are sick people we're
dealing with.
But to every COVID tyrant who
wants to take away our freedom,
hear these words,
we will not comply.
So don't even think about it.
We will not shut down our
schools.
We will not accept your
lockdowns.
We will not abide by your mask
mandates, and we will not
tolerate your vaccine mandates.
They rigged the 2020 election,
and now they're trying to do the
same thing all over again by
rigging the most important
election in the history of our
country, the 2024 election,
even if it means trying to bring
back COVID.
But they will fail because we
will not let it happen.
When I'm back in the White
House, I will use every
available authority to cut
federal funding to any school,
college, airline or public
transportation system that
imposes a mask mandate or a
vaccine mandate.
Thank you very much.